♪ It's a little bit funny
this feeling inside ♪
♪ I'm not one of those
who can easily hide ♪
♪ I don't have much
money, but, boy if I did ♪
♪ I'd buy a big house
where we both could live ♪
♪ If I was a sculptor,
but then again, no ♪
♪ Or a man who makes potions
in a traveling show ♪
♪ I know it's not much, but
it's the best I can do ♪
♪ My gift is my song,
and this one's for you ♪
♪ And you can tell everybody
this is your song ♪
♪ It may be quite simple,
but now that it's done ♪
♪ I hope you don't mind,
I hope you don't mind ♪
♪ That I put down in words ♪
♪ How wonderful life is
while you're in the world ♪
♪ I sat on the roof and
kicked off the moss ♪
♪ Well, a few of the verses ♪
♪ Well, they've got me quite cross ♪
♪ But the sun's been quite
kind while I wrote this song ♪
♪ It's for people like you
that keep it turned on ♪
♪ So excuse me forgetting,
but these things I do ♪
♪ You see, I've forgotten if
they're green or they're blue ♪
♪ Anyway, the thing is,
what I really mean ♪
♪ Yours are the sweetest
eyes I've ever seen ♪
♪ And you can tell everybody
this is your song ♪
♪ It may be quite simple,
but now that it's done ♪
♪ I hope you don't mind,
I hope you don't mind ♪
♪ That I put down in words ♪
♪ How wonderful life is
while you're in the world ♪
♪ I hope you don't mind,
I hope you don't mind ♪
♪ That I put down in words ♪
♪ How wonderful life is
while you're in the world ♪